RG 062:056, Town of Granby
Connecticut State Library
Town of Granby records
1797-1948
Connecticut State Library
Granby (Conn.)
13 cubic feet
Administrative, school, and tax records for the town of Granby.
RG062_056
T000325
Historical Note
The town of Granby was incorporated in October 1786 and was taken from Simsbury.
Scope and Content
Administrative, school, and tax records for the town of Granby.
Index Terms
Subjects:
School enrollment -- Connecticut -- Granby -- Statistics; Deeds -- Connecticut -- Granby; Tax assessment -- Connecticut -- Granby -- Registers; Taxation -- Connecticut -- Granby -- Registers; Local taxation -- Connecticut -- Granby -- Registers; Property tax -- Connecticut -- Granby -- Registers
Places:
Granby (Conn.) -- Records and correspondence
Restrictions on Access
Box 7 is restricted due to condition. Please contact State Archives staff for assistance.
These records are stored at an off-site facility and therefore may not be available on a same-day basis.
See the policy.
Container List
- Records, 1797-1948
  - School registers, 1927-1943 (Box Boxes 1-4)
  - School district committee reports and financial records, 1856-1872 (Box Box 5)
  - Town records, including bills from Newgate Prison, orders for payment, deeds, executions, 1797-1827 (Box Box 5)
  - Tax abstracts, 1857-1948
    Box 12 is located on oversize shelving.
    - 1857, 1858, 1862, 1863, 1865 (Box Box 6)
    - 1878, 1879, 1880, 1881, 1882 (Box Box 7)
      Restricted due to condition.
    - 1876, 1877, 1883, 1884, 1885, 1886, 1887 (Box Box 8)
    - 1888, 1889, 1890, 1891, 1892, 1893, 1894, 1895 (Box Box 9)
    - 1896, 1897, 1898, 1899, 1900, 1901, 1902, 1903 (Box Box 10)
    - 1904, 1905, 1906, 1907, 1908, 1909, 1910, 1911 (Box Box 11)
    - 1914, 1915, 1916 (Box Box 12)
    - 1912, 1913, 1917, 1918, 1919, 1920, 1921 (Box Box 13)
    - 1922, 1923, 1924, 1925, 1926 (Box Box 14)
    - 1927, 1928, 1929, 1930, 1931, 1932 (Box Box 15)
    - 1933, 1934, 1935, 1936, 1937 (Box Box 16)
    - 1938, 1939, 1940, 1941, 1942, 1943 (Box Box 17)
    - 1944, 1945, 1946, 1947, 1948 (Box Box 18)